<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
            <string name="updates_description_heading">
        "Description"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_description">
        "A common mistake that is easy to prevent and can result in serious consequences, "
        "is installing the latest updates for software. This applied to all device such as smartphones, "
        "tablets, laptops, computers, and other house hold devices that are network connected. "
        "These should be kept up to date at all times. The updates will often be for Operating Systems "
        "(E.g. Android or Windows) and software. Applying the updates is quick, easy, and free. \n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_patching_title">
        "Also known as ‘patching'"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_patching">
       "Manufacturers and developers regularly releases updates which not only add additional "
        "features and functionality, but improve the overall security for the devices. "
        "This may include the fixing of known vulnerabilities that could potentially be exploited by an attacker. \n\n"
        "Applying these updates is one of the most important things to do to improves the devices overall security. "
        "If you wish to stay secure, most software will include an automatic update option which is beneficial to be "
        "enabled wherever possible. This will ensure that updates are installed in a timely manner when they are released. \n\n"
        "However, all IT has a lifespan. When the software becomes obsolete and the manufacturer is no longer providing updates, "
        "it is highly recommended to replace this software. An example of this is old operating systems such as Windows XP. \n"\n

    </string>

    <string name="updates_resources">
        "Helpful Resources"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_url1_desc">
        "The importance of software updates and patches \n"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_url1">
        "https://us.norton.com/internetsecurity-how-to-the-importance-of-general-software-updates-and-patches.html \n"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_url2_desc">
        "Guidance on obsolete platform security guidance  \n"
    </string>

    <string name="updates_url2">
        "https://www.ncsc.gov.uk/guidance/obsolete-platforms-security-guidance \n"
    </string>
</resources>