<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="passwords_description_title">"Description"</string>
    <string name="passwords_description">
        "Laptops, computers, household network devices, and smartphones may contain critical "
        "data such as personal information, and details of online accounts you access. "
        "It is essential that this data is not available to unauthorised users."
        "When implemented correctly, passwords are an effective way of securing devices.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="passwords_discovery_title">"Password Discovery Methods"</string>

    <string name="passwords_discovery">
        "Many techniques can be utilised to discover passwords. Popular approaches may include the following:\n\n"
        "1) Social engineering. For example, phishing; coercion.\n\n"
        "2) Manual password guessing. This often includes personal information such as names, and date of birth.\n\n"
        "3) Brute-force attacks. This consists of automating a large number of password guesses until the correct one is found.\n\n"
        "4) Compromisation  of a database that contains passwords"\n\n
        "5) Intercepting a password during transmit. Plaintext passwords should not be used during transmit. HTTPS should be used"
        "as this will obfuscate information during transmit"\n\n
        "6) Compromising passwords that have been stored insecurely; such as written on paper or stored in a file that could potentially be retrieved by an attacker"\n\n</string>

    <string name="password_tips_title">"Tips to help secure passwords"</string>

    <string name="password_tips_1_title">
        "Tip 1: Ensure you enable password protection \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_1">
         "A screenlock password, PIN, or other forms of authentication such as fingerprint should always be used.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_2_title">
        "Tip 2: Change all default passwords \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_2">
        "This is a common mistake, and very dangerous. A recent Ransomware attack was able to control hundreds of thousands"
        "of devices by testing for default passwords. Default passwords for systems and software should always be changed."
        "Essential devices include routers, wireless access points, and firewalls.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_3_title">
        "Tip 3: Use two-factor authentication for important accounts \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_3">
        "If an option is available to use two factor authentication (2FA), it is highly recommended to use it as it adds a "
        large amount of additional security for not much effort. " 2FA required that you use two different methods to 'prove' your "
        "identity before you can use a service. This usually includes a password combined with another method such as "
        "an sms code sent to a smartphone, a code sent to an email address, that must be entered in addition to the password.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_4_title">
       "Tip 4: Avoid using predictable passwords \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_4">
        "Passwords should be easy to remember but hard for somebody else to guess. Passwords should contains: \n"
        "- A minimum of 1 lowercase letter [a-z] \n"
        "- A minimum of 1 uppercase letter [A-Z] \n"
        "- A minimum of 1 numeric character [0-9] \n"
        "- A minimum or 1 special character (~`!@#$%^&amp;*()-_+={}[]|\\;:\",./?) \n"
        "- A minimum of 8 characters in length \n\n"
        "Examples of weak passwords: \n"
        "1) password \n"
        "2) 12345678 \n"
        "3) qwerty \n\n"
        "Examples of strong password: \n"
        "1) blu3@T0p \n"
        "2) cash$C0w \n"
        "3) not7Th!s\n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tips_5_title">
        "Tip 5: Do not use the same passwords for all your accounts \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_tip_5">
        "Do not use the same password for all your logins. As this may be hard to remember, "
        "password managers are helpful tools that generate random strong password"
        "and store them so you do not have to remember them yourself. The only password "
        "required that you remember is the master password. This is the password that protects"
        "all your other passwords and therefore should be secure. \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_resources">
        "Helpful Resources"
    </string>

    <string name="password_url1_desc">
        "This list contains 100 of the worst passwords used in 2017. These passwords must not be used "
        "as attackers will often try these first.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_url1">
        "https://www.teamsid.com/worst-passwords-2017-full-list/ \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_url2_desc">
        "This document provides guidance for using strong passwords \n"
    </string>

    <string name="password_url2">
        "https://www.ncsc.gov.uk/guidance/password-guidance-simplifying-your-approach \n"
    </string>
</resources>